<!--
 Copyright (C) 2013 Rusty Gerard

 This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 (at your option) any later version.

 This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 GNU General Public License for more details.

 You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 -->

<gameData>
    <loadingScreen>
 Loading. Please wait...</loadingScreen>
    <splashScreen>
                                                                               
  *                             #     #                            ####  ##    
   *                 ***        ##   ##           ##               ##  # ##    
   **               *****       ### ###       ##  ##               ##  # ##    
    ***             ******      ####### ## # #### #####  ###   ### ####  ##    
    *****          *** ****     ## # ##  # #  ##  ##  # ## ## ##   ## #  ##    
     ******       ****   ***    ##   ##  # #  ##  ##  # ## ##   ## ##  # ##    
     *** ****     **      ***   ##   ##  ###   ## ##  #  ###  ###  ##  # ##### 
      **   ***** ***        **            #                                    
       **     *****          **          #                                     
       ***        *****       **                  **                           
        ** *   **      *********        **********                             
         ** *  *       *       **  ************                                
          *   **        *        *       ****                                  
          **  *       * *   **** **    ****                                    
           *  *    **   **     *  *   ***                                      
             *   **    ****   *     ***                                        
             *  ***    ***  **    ***                                          
             * *  ***** ***      **                                            
            **  *              **   ***                                        
            **   **          ***     **                                        
            **    **        **       ***                                       
            **     **     ***         **                                       
           ***      ***  **           ***                                      
           **        *****             **                                      
           **         ****       *   * **                                      
           *            ***  *  ***   * **                                     
           *        **   ******    *    **                                     
           *       ***     ******    * ****                                    
           *      ***       ***** *      **                                    
           **    ***          *****      **                                    
           **   ***             ***** ******                                   
          ***  ***                **********                                   
          *** ***                    *******                                   
          *******                       *****                                  
           *****                                                               
           ****                                                                
           ***                                                                 
           **                                                                  
           **                                                                  
                                                                               
                                                                               
                                                                               
                                                                               
                                                                               
                                                                               
                                                Copyright (c) 2013 Rusty Gerard
    </splashScreen>
    <introduction>
        It all started in the autumn of 1925 in the sleepy city of Arkham,
        Massachusetts. The men had set off to work, students were headed to class
        at Miskatonic University, and you thought it was going to be another
        routine patrol. You even brought bread crumbs to feed the birds. Of
        course, that was until strange happenings started cropping up all over.


        Farmer Akeley called the station to report that he had seen some sort of
        "Pinkish things that were about five feet long, with crustacous bodies"
        out on his property. It was dismissed out of hand until more reports came
        from all over the city, even the Mayor. That was when the the Sheriff
        rounded up all able-bodied men and women to investigate the situation.


        At first no one knew from where these mysterious arcane powers were
        coming from but all of the signs lead you to the University District.
        It was then that you realized the powers were emanating from the very
        campus itself.


        Upon arriving onto the scene you notice a man running in a blind panic
        from the main building. Selecting you out of the crowd at random, he
        grabs you by the arm and frantically spouts nonsense about some book
        called the "Necronomicon:"


        "It was stolen from the archives last night! It must be recovered! Only
        then will the chaos stop and the University be set back to its original
        state!" Explaining that he is the University Library's archivist, the
        old man pushes a mysterious object into your hands and implores you to
        enter the main building at once.


        Armed only with your service revolver and a hand-written journal filled
        with arcane lore that you do not comprehend, are you brave enough to do
        battle with the horrors that lurk within the non-Euclidean labyrinth to
        recover the Necronomicon and bring the chaos to an end in Arkham?
    </introduction>
    <legalNotice>
        Copyright (C) 2013 Rusty Gerard

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see &lt;http://www.gnu.org/licenses/&gt;.
    </legalNotice>
    <instructions>
        CONTROLS
        Arrow keys and numbers control movement. Press 5 to wait.

        7 8 9     &#8598; &#8593; &#8599;

        4 5 6     &#8592;   &#8594;

        1 2 3     &#8601; &#8595; &#8600;

        COMMANDS
        g Grab an item
        G Grab an item quickly
        d Drop an item
        D Drop an item quickly
        i View inventory
        u Use an item in your inventory
        e Equip an item in your inventory
        r Remove an equipped item and place it in your inventory
        R Remove ammunition from an item in your inventory
        l Load ammunition into a weapon
        f Fire a projectile weapon
        c Chat with an adjacent NPC
        ? Display this screen
        Q Quit the game

        SPACEBAR Toggles between display modes -or-
        targets when aiming a projectile.

        HOW TO KILL STUFF
        Bump into a monster to attack it, or press (f)ire to aim a projectile
        weapon at it.
    </instructions>
    <playerFile>/data/7DRL2013/player.xml</playerFile>
    <startingAreaFile>/data/7DRL2013/maps/miskatonicUniversity.xml</startingAreaFile>
    <factionDataFile>/data/7DRL2013/factionData.xml</factionDataFile>
    <itemListFiles>
        <itemListFile>/data/7DRL2013/items/armor.xml</itemListFile>
        <itemListFile>/data/7DRL2013/items/books.xml</itemListFile>
        <itemListFile>/data/7DRL2013/items/miscellany.xml</itemListFile>
        <itemListFile>/data/7DRL2013/items/weapons.xml</itemListFile>
    </itemListFiles>
    <npcListFiles>
        <npcListFile>/data/7DRL2013/npcs/townsfolk.xml</npcListFile>
        <npcListFile>/data/7DRL2013/npcs/monsters.xml</npcListFile>
    </npcListFiles>
    <splashForeground>0x0000FF</splashForeground>
    <splashBackground>0x000000</splashBackground>
    <boxForeground>0x696969</boxForeground>
    <boxBackground>0x000000</boxBackground>
    <fontForeground>0xE6E6FA</fontForeground>
    <fontBackground>0x000000</fontBackground>
    <selectForeground>0x000000</selectForeground>
    <selectBackground>0xE6E6FA</selectBackground>
</gameData>
