<!--
 Copyright (C) 2013 Rusty Gerard

 This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 (at your option) any later version.

 This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 GNU General Public License for more details.

 You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 -->

<itemList id="books">
    <ItemData id="old_journal">
        <character>"</character>
        <color>0x8B4513</color>
        <inventoriableData>
            <name>Old Journal</name>
            <description>An old, leatherbound journal.</description>
            <maxPerSlot>1</maxPerSlot>
            <value>0</value>
        </inventoriableData>
        <useableData>
            <disposable>false</disposable>
            <loadable>false</loadable>
            <maximumCapacity>-1</maximumCapacity>
            <useMessage>
She is the Lord of the Wood, even to the end of time and the gifts of the
men of Leng. So from the wells of night to the gulfs of space, and from
the gulfs of space to the wells of night, ever the praises of Great
Cthulhu, of Tsathoggua, and of Him Who is not to be Named. Ever Their
praises, and abundance to the Black Goat of the Woods. Ia! Shub-Niggurath!
The Goat with a Thousand Young! Ia! Shub-Niggurath! The Black Goat of the
Woods with a Thousand Young!


And it has come to pass that the Lord of the Woods, being accompanied by
seven and nine, down the onyx steps bringing tributes to Him in the Gulf,
Azathoth, He of Whom Thou has taught us marvels innumerable. On the wings
of night out beyond space, out beyond the Abyss, to That whereof Yuggoth
is the youngest child, rolling alone in black aether at the rim.


Go out among men and find the ways thereof, that He in the Gulf may know.
To Nyarlathotep, Mighty Messenger, must all things be told. And He shall
put on the semblance of men, the waxen mask and the robe that hides, and
come down from the world of Seven Suns to mock us.


Nyarlathotep, Great Messenger, bringer of strange joy to Yuggoth through
the void, Father of the Million Favoured Ones, Stalker among the night.</useMessage>
        </useableData>
    </ItemData>
    <ItemData id="necronomicon">
        <character>"</character>
        <color>0x000000</color>
        <inventoriableData>
            <name>The Necronomicon</name>
            <description>A massive tome bound in leather with two iron clasps.</description>
            <maxPerSlot>1</maxPerSlot>
            <value>0</value>
        </inventoriableData>
        <useableData>
            <disposable>false</disposable>
            <loadable>false</loadable>
            <maximumCapacity>-1</maximumCapacity>
            <useMessage>To read this tome of forbidden lore would surely lead to madness.</useMessage>
        </useableData>
    </ItemData>
</itemList>
